

DHANASHRI CHIMULE

CUSTOMER SUPPORT EXECUTIVE

Profile

I am a qualified and professional customer support and digital marketing executive with three years of experience in customer service and freelancing for digital marketing .Strong communication

and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR CUSTOMER SUPPORT **REPRESENTATIVE**

American Express

Feb 2022- Nov 2023

• Senior customer support representative Non-Voice U.S. Market,

CUSTOMER SUPPORT EXECUTIVE

Teleperformance

Feb 2021- Jan 2022

• Customer support executive for international process in billing department for Comcast (Xfinity) Non-Voice U.S. Market.

CUSTOMER SUPPORT EXECUTIVE

Tech Mahindra

July 2020 to Jan 2021

• Worked as a customer support executive on contact basis for Flipkart

9930106064

dhanashri.chimule09@gmail.com

D/4 society no 30, Mhada, Malvani, Malad west.

EDUCATION

TOLANI COLLEGE

BFM Bechelor of financial markets 2019-2023

VALIA COLLEGE

High school commerce field

2016-2018

SKILLS

- Ms. Word, Ms. Excel, Ms. Office
- Email servicing
- Virtual servers.
- · Great communication skills
- Fluent in Englis, Hindi, Marathi & basic skills in French, Punjabi.
- Social media marketing